Privacy Policy | The Institute for Creation Research                           

=======================================================================

Privacy Policy
==============

The Institute for Creation Research (ICR) will not give or sell personal information that you enter on our website. In addition, ICR protects our donor information, including information obtained through the website, emails, traditional mail, phone, live events, and/or any other contact. ICR will never share or sell this information with any outside party.

No information is collected by our website other than data that is typically collected by websites in general. If you choose to provide additional information, such as signing up for a free subscription, this will allow us to serve you better.

Any personal information provided to a legitimate agent of ICR (such as to enable mailings or credit card transactions) will be limited to a “need to know” restricted access. Our agents are bound by fiduciary laws to protect your personal information from unauthorized use.

ICR uses audience data from Google Analytics to improve our websites and mobile apps. [Click here](http://www.google.com/goodtoknow) for more information on managing the data your browser shares with Google.

If you no longer wish to receive our email publications, please [click here](http://www.icr.org/change) to unsubscribe. To request removal from our print mailing list, please send your name and postal address to [subscriptions@icr.org](mailto:subscriptions@icr.org).

This site is informational and educational in nature. It is not offering professional legal, tax, or accounting advice on your estate. All persons who use information from this site must be advised by qualified professional counsel. For specific advice about your estate, please consult a qualified professional advisor.

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please [contact us](mailto:webmaster@icr.org?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20Question&body=Regarding%20your%20privacy%20policy%20at%20http%3A//icr.org/home/privacy%2C%20...).

Return to our [subscription form](https://www.icr.org/subscriptions).

More The Universe Was Created

Tonight’s (April 7) full moon is special because it occurs when the moon is close to perigee, the point in its orbit where it is closest to Earth.1,2...

BY: [JAKE HEBERT, PH.D.](https://www.icr.org/home?search=AdvancedSearch&f_keyword_all=&f_context_all=any&f_context_exact=any&f_context_any=any&f_context_without=any&f_search_type=articles&section=0&f_constraint=both&=Search&module=home&action=submitsearch&f_authorID=218)

This month (July 2020), multiple astronomical objects highlight God’s glory displayed in the heavens.1 For the next two weeks, all...

BY: [JAKE HEBERT, PH.D.](https://www.icr.org/home?search=AdvancedSearch&f_keyword_all=&f_context_all=any&f_context_exact=any&f_context_any=any&f_context_without=any&f_search_type=articles&section=0&f_constraint=both&=Search&module=home&action=submitsearch&f_authorID=218)

Using computer simulations, a team of researchers has concluded the planet Venus could still be geologically active.1,2 The scientists used...

BY: [JAKE HEBERT, PH.D.](https://www.icr.org/home?search=AdvancedSearch&f_keyword_all=&f_context_all=any&f_context_exact=any&f_context_any=any&f_context_without=any&f_search_type=articles&section=0&f_constraint=both&=Search&module=home&action=submitsearch&f_authorID=218)

More The Universe Is Stable

Astronomers have determined that a distant galaxy discovered three years ago is rotating, making it the most distant rotating disk galaxy yet observed.1...

BY: [JAKE HEBERT, PH.D.](https://www.icr.org/home?search=AdvancedSearch&f_keyword_all=&f_context_all=any&f_context_exact=any&f_context_any=any&f_context_without=any&f_search_type=articles&section=0&f_constraint=both&=Search&module=home&action=submitsearch&f_authorID=218)

For families seeking worthwhile home-based science activities, Comet SWAN presents another opportunity to do some backyard astronomy and to celebrate God’s...

BY: [JAKE HEBERT, PH.D.](https://www.icr.org/home?search=AdvancedSearch&f_keyword_all=&f_context_all=any&f_context_exact=any&f_context_any=any&f_context_without=any&f_search_type=articles&section=0&f_constraint=both&=Search&module=home&action=submitsearch&f_authorID=218)

Evolutionary astronomers have a problem. The universe is expanding at an ever-increasing rate, but if general relativity is an accurate cosmological model,...

BY: [BRIAN THOMAS, PH.D.](https://www.icr.org/home?search=AdvancedSearch&f_keyword_all=&f_context_all=any&f_context_exact=any&f_context_any=any&f_context_without=any&f_search_type=articles&section=0&f_constraint=both&=Search&module=home&action=submitsearch&f_authorID=201)

More Astronomy

Secular scientists are obsessed with attempting to show that life on Earth is not unique and therefore must exist, if not elsewhere in our solar system...

BY: [FRANK SHERWIN, D.SC. (HON.)](https://www.icr.org/home?search=AdvancedSearch&f_keyword_all=&f_context_all=any&f_context_exact=any&f_context_any=any&f_context_without=any&f_search_type=articles&section=0&f_constraint=both&=Search&module=home&action=submitsearch&f_authorID=32)

Well, there goes another star, disappearing into the night as if it had never existed. For an entire year, Hubble scientists used the space telescope to...

BY: [BRIAN THOMAS, PH.D.](https://www.icr.org/home?search=AdvancedSearch&f_keyword_all=&f_context_all=any&f_context_exact=any&f_context_any=any&f_context_without=any&f_search_type=articles&section=0&f_constraint=both&=Search&module=home&action=submitsearch&f_authorID=201)

Tonight’s (April 7) full moon is special because it occurs when the moon is close to perigee, the point in its orbit where it is closest to Earth.1,2...

BY: [JAKE HEBERT, PH.D.](https://www.icr.org/home?search=AdvancedSearch&f_keyword_all=&f_context_all=any&f_context_exact=any&f_context_any=any&f_context_without=any&f_search_type=articles&section=0&f_constraint=both&=Search&module=home&action=submitsearch&f_authorID=218)

More Physics

Many famous secular physicists claim we don’t need a Creator to explain the universe’s origin. They say “the laws of physics...

BY: [JAKE HEBERT, PH.D.](https://www.icr.org/home?search=AdvancedSearch&f_keyword_all=&f_context_all=any&f_context_exact=any&f_context_any=any&f_context_without=any&f_search_type=articles&section=0&f_constraint=both&=Search&module=home&action=submitsearch&f_authorID=218)

Explaining the origin of the universe is an enormous challenge for those seeking to deny their Creator: How could a universe come from nothing? The...

BY: [JAKE HEBERT, PH.D.](https://www.icr.org/home?search=AdvancedSearch&f_keyword_all=&f_context_all=any&f_context_exact=any&f_context_any=any&f_context_without=any&f_search_type=articles&section=0&f_constraint=both&=Search&module=home&action=submitsearch&f_authorID=218)

Aided by a supercomputer, an international team of theoretical physicists has recently performed a massive computation that confirmed Einstein’s...

BY: [BRIAN THOMAS, PH.D.](https://www.icr.org/home?search=AdvancedSearch&f_keyword_all=&f_context_all=any&f_context_exact=any&f_context_any=any&f_context_without=any&f_search_type=articles&section=0&f_constraint=both&=Search&module=home&action=submitsearch&f_authorID=201)

More Contrasting Worldviews

This summer, the Hubble Space Telescope took a brilliant new photograph of Saturn and its rings.1 Saturn’s moons Mimas and Enceladus can...

BY: [JAKE HEBERT, PH.D.](https://www.icr.org/home?search=AdvancedSearch&f_keyword_all=&f_context_all=any&f_context_exact=any&f_context_any=any&f_context_without=any&f_search_type=articles&section=0&f_constraint=both&=Search&module=home&action=submitsearch&f_authorID=218)

The recent discovery of a tiny tyrannosaur jaw bone fragment and a claw has some scientists again pushing dinosaurs as birds.1 But is there...

BY: [TIM CLAREY, PH.D.](https://www.icr.org/home?search=AdvancedSearch&f_keyword_all=&f_context_all=any&f_context_exact=any&f_context_any=any&f_context_without=any&f_search_type=articles&section=0&f_constraint=both&=Search&module=home&action=submitsearch&f_authorID=176)

In an executive order, dated May 1, 2020, our president made this declaration: I, DONALD J. TRUMP, President of the United States of America, find...

BY: [REBECCA MORRIS BARBER](https://www.icr.org/home?search=AdvancedSearch&f_keyword_all=&f_context_all=any&f_context_exact=any&f_context_any=any&f_context_without=any&f_search_type=articles&section=0&f_constraint=both&=Search&module=home&action=submitsearch&f_authorID=243)

More Science

John Walton is an influential Old Testament theologian at Wheaton College with an unorthodox and non-literal view of Genesis.1 He is also an...

BY: [JEFFREY P. TOMKINS, PH.D.](https://www.icr.org/home?search=AdvancedSearch&f_keyword_all=&f_context_all=any&f_context_exact=any&f_context_any=any&f_context_without=any&f_search_type=articles&section=0&f_constraint=both&=Search&module=home&action=submitsearch&f_authorID=207)

An overview of the Milankovitch (or astronomical) ice age theory appears in the May 2020 issue of Physics Today.1 This theory (hypothesis, really)...

BY: [JAKE HEBERT, PH.D.](https://www.icr.org/home?search=AdvancedSearch&f_keyword_all=&f_context_all=any&f_context_exact=any&f_context_any=any&f_context_without=any&f_search_type=articles&section=0&f_constraint=both&=Search&module=home&action=submitsearch&f_authorID=218)

Brain researchers from San Diego State University have just reported digitally capturing the dense folds of a preserved human cerebellum using a high resolution...

BY: [BRIAN THOMAS, PH.D.](https://www.icr.org/home?search=AdvancedSearch&f_keyword_all=&f_context_all=any&f_context_exact=any&f_context_any=any&f_context_without=any&f_search_type=articles&section=0&f_constraint=both&=Search&module=home&action=submitsearch&f_authorID=201)

More Creation Science Update

The InSight robotic lander found evidence in the interior of Mars for the existence of an active giant mantle plume, a large blob of molten rock that...

BY: [JAKE HEBERT, PH.D.](https://www.icr.org/home?search=AdvancedSearch&f_keyword_all=&f_context_all=any&f_context_exact=any&f_context_any=any&f_context_without=any&f_search_type=articles&section=0&f_constraint=both&=Search&module=home&action=submitsearch&f_authorID=218)

To be spatially capable creatures, humans need their brains to tell them 1) where things are in relation to themselves and 2) where everything is in...

BY: [JONATHAN K. CORRADO, PH.D., P. E.](https://www.icr.org/home?search=AdvancedSearch&f_keyword_all=&f_context_all=any&f_context_exact=any&f_context_any=any&f_context_without=any&f_search_type=articles&section=0&f_constraint=both&=Search&module=home&action=submitsearch&f_authorID=251)

Recently, a fossil believed to be a juvenile duck-billed dinosaur was found in a hillside in Dinosaur Provincial Park, Canada. The scientists discovered...

BY: [FRANK SHERWIN, D.SC. (HON.)](https://www.icr.org/home?search=AdvancedSearch&f_keyword_all=&f_context_all=any&f_context_exact=any&f_context_any=any&f_context_without=any&f_search_type=articles&section=0&f_constraint=both&=Search&module=home&action=submitsearch&f_authorID=32)

_As a federally recognized 501(c)(3) nonprofit ministry of the USA, all gifts to ICR are completely tax deductible to the fullest extent allowed by U.S. law._

[Use Policy](https://www.icr.org/home/copyright)•[Privacy Policy](https://www.icr.org/home/privacy)•[Subscriptions](https://www.icr.org/subscriptions)•[Contact](https://www.icr.org/contact)

Content ©2024 Institute for Creation Research

* Close

#### ICR Menu

* [Social  
    Media](#)
